<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<?xml-model href="https://wofsauge.github.io/isaac-xml-validator/xsd/metadata.xsd" ?>
<metadata>
  <name>Hatsune Miku (+Tainted)</name>
  <directory>isaac-miku</directory>
  <description>
    [h1]Hatsune Miku (+Tainted)[/h1]

A standalone character mod for The Binding of Isaac featuring Hatsune Miku and her tainted counterpart!

[h1]TAINTED MIKU FIXED FOR VANILLA[/h1]

Now when playing Vanilla Rep+, Tainted Miku's Lost Notes drops should work as intended!

[h1]INFO[/h1]
I get a lot of comments like the games not launching or the mod breaks the game. Make sure you have all DLCs!

----------------------------------------------------------------------
[h2]Features[/h2]

[b]Hatsune Miku[/b]
• Attacks with her voice with tears that resemble notes.
• Each hit has a chance to [b]Charm[/b] enemies.
• [b]Birthright Effect:[/b] Charmed enemies have a chance to permanently become your loyal [b]Fans[/b]! (until they die)
• Use her active item, the [b]Microphone[/b], to inspire your audience!

[b]Tainted Miku (Work In Progress)[/b]
• Having lost her voice, she starts the run firing highly unstable [b]Glitch Notes[/b].
• Slain enemies drop [b]Lost Notes[/b] onto the floor.
• Collecting different Lost Notes grants various dynamic gameplay effects.
• Use the [b]Broken Microphone[/b] to rapidly switch melodies.

----------------------------------------------------------------------
[h2]Mod Compatibility[/h2]

• [b]External Item Descriptions (EID):[/b] Full native support is included!
• Notice any missing or incorrect descriptions? Please leave a comment.

----------------------------------------------------------------------
[h2]Planned[/h2]

• Finish and balance Tainted Miku's core gameplay loop.
• Implement a unique Birthright effect for Tainted Miku.
• Design and add more Miku-themed items to the item pools.
• Upgrade custom sprites, animations, and special visual effects.
• Overall balance tweaks and mechanical improvements.

You can checkout the Github Repository here [url=https://github.com/vulpya/isaac-miku]Source Code[/url]

----------------------------------------------------------------------
[h2]Disclaimer[/h2]

This is a non-commercial, fan-made mod created as a personal project for fun. All characters, names, and related properties belong to their original creators. This project is not affiliated with or endorsed by any official rights holders.

----------------------------------------------------------------------
[h2]Special Thanks[/h2]

• [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198102520074]ale[/url] — For creating the amazing Miku/Vocaloid sprites!
• [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/thearexz]Arexz[/url] — For helping with custom sprite editing and refinement.
  </description>
  <version>0.3.1</version>
  <visibility />
</metadata>
